Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- G
  - Georgakis, Christos, undated; cuid1329 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Georgi, Gunter, undated; cuid1330 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Gerhardt, Kenneth C., undated; cuid1331 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Gersten, Marvin C., 1980; cuid1332 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Gertler, Janos, undated; cuid1333 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Geva, Eran, 2009; cuid1334 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Ghandehari, Masoud, undated; cuid1335 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Giacobello, Bartholemew F., 1981; cuid1336 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Giba, John, 1966, 1993, 1995; cuid1337 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Gilbert, Jack, undated; cuid1338 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Gilbert, John, undated; cuid1339 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Gillett, Elizabeth R.H., undated; cuid1340 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Gillette, David, 2001; cuid1341 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gilmont, Roger, 1991; cuid1342 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Giordano, Anthony B. (and wife Peggy), circa 1950, 1996; cuid1343 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Glenn, Alvin B., undated; cuid1344 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Gluckman, Joshua, undated; cuid1345 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Gobran, Riad, undated; cuid1346 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Gold, Albert, 1978; cuid1347 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Gold, Bernard, 1998; cuid1348 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Gold, Lawrence, 1975; cuid1349 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Gold, Louis, undated; cuid1350 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Goldberg, Samuel David, 1968; cuid1351 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Golden, William T., undated; cuid1352 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Goldin, Daniel S., 1992; cuid1353 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Goldman, David S., undated; cuid1354 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Goldman, Irwin, 1977; cuid1355 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Goldman, Jack, undated; cuid1356 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Goldmark, Peter C., undated; cuid1357 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Goldsmith, Clifford Henry, 1996, 1998, 2001; cuid1358 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Goldstein, Harvey, 1993; cuid1359 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Goldstein, Matthew, undated; cuid1360 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Goodman, David J., 1999; cuid1361 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Goodman, Murray, undated; cuid1362 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Gordon, Emmet F., undated; cuid1363 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Gordon, Jayne, circa 1996; cuid1364 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Gould, Gordon, undated; cuid1365 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Grad, Arthur, 1971; cuid1366 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Granato, Richardson, undated; cuid1367 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Granis, Michael, 1957; cuid1368 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Grantz, Howard E., undated; cuid1369 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Grau, Herman, undated; cuid1370 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Gray, Lucille R., undated; cuid1371 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Gray, Nomer, undated; 9 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Grayson, Laurence, 1986; cuid1372 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Greco, William J., undated; cuid1373 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Green, Mark, 1994, 2002; cuid1374 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Greene, Barry, cuid1375 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Greenfield, S. Steve, 1988; cuid1376 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Greenshields, Bruce D., undated; cuid1377 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Greenwood, Doug, undated; cuid1378 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Gregor, Harry, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1964; cuid1379 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Grieco, Linda, undated; cuid1380 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Griemsmann, John, undated; cuid1381 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Griffis, Fletcher H. "Bud", 1999, 2000; cuid1382 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Grill, Jeanette, undated; cuid1383 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Gross, Richard A., 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2004; cuid1384 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gross, S.H., 1967; cuid1385 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Grossman, undated; cuid1386 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Grossman, Fred, 1978; cuid1387 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gruber, Helmut, 1986; cuid1388 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gruehr, Anatole R., 1956; cuid1389 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Guadalupe, Magda, undated; cuid3616 (Box 4, Folder 6B)
  - Guerrieri, Anne, undated; cuid1390 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gugick, Leonard, undated; cuid1391 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guglielmi, Marco, 1986; cuid1392 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gupta, Sunil, circa 1996; cuid1393 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- H
  - Haas, Zygmunt, undated; cuid1394 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Habach, George F., undated; cuid1395 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Haddad, Richard, undated; cuid1396 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hadimioglu, H., undated; cuid1397 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hague, Bernard, 1929; cuid1398 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hall, 1958; cuid1399 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hallingby, Paul Jr., undated; cuid1400 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Halpern, Gregory, 1982; cuid1401 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hammoud, Harry P., undated; cuid1402 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hampden, Walter, undated; cuid1403 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Han, Chang Dae "Paul", 1974, 1986; cuid1404 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hancock, Herbie, 2002; cuid1405 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hanson, Jimmy, undated; cuid1406 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hao, Xiaolong, undated; cuid1407 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Harazim, William, 1974; cuid1408 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Harker, David (1906-1991), undated; cuid1409 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Harris, Wanda, circa 1996; cuid1410 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Harrison, Gen, 1953; cuid1411 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Harrington, Paul R., undated; cuid1412 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Harrison, Shelley A., 1994; cuid1413 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hartigan, Ellen F., circa 1990; cuid1414 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hase, Leopold, undated; cuid1415 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hastak, Makarand, undated; cuid1416 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Hauser, Norbert, undated; cuid1417 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hausmann, Erich, undated; cuid1418 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Hayes, Christopher, undated; cuid1419 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hebbert, C. Mark, circa 1955; cuid1420 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hechhouse, Phil, undated; cuid1421 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Heckman, Leila, 1997; cuid1422 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Heinzelman, Fred, 1960, 1982; cuid1423 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Hellerstein, Lisa, undated; cuid1424 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Henderson, Annette, 1978; cuid1425 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Henkel, Herbert L., 1999; cuid1426 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hennessey, Raymond G., 1974; cuid1427 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Henry, Otto, 1960; cuid1428 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Herbach, L., undated; cuid1429 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Herbst, Marc, undated; cuid1430 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Herr, Barber, undated; cuid1431 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Hertzberg, Constantine, 1990s; cuid1432 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Hessel, Alexander, undated; cuid1433 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Hewlett, William R., 1975; cuid1434 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Heyke, John E., Jr., undated; cuid1435 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Hibben, Samuel G., undated; cuid1436 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Hielscher, Andreas, undated; cuid1437 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Hiller, Maruin H., 1975; cuid1438 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hinkaty, Charles J., 1997; cuid1439 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hinte, Fred, 1980; cuid1440 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Hirayama, Kozo, 1978; cuid1441 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Hoadley, George B., undated; cuid1442 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Hochman, Jack, undated; cuid1443 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Hochstadt, Harry, 1964, 1988; cuid1444 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Hockney, Donald, 1979, 1982, 1986, circa 1996; cuid1445 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hoff, Nicholas J., 1953, 1956; cuid1446 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Hoffman, Harmon F., undated; cuid1447 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hoiberg, Svend, undated; cuid1448 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Holloway, Helen, 1959; cuid1449 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Holub, Helen and Helene, 1954; cuid1450 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Holzmacher, Robert G., undated; cuid1451 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Homberger, Conrad, undated; cuid1452 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hommer, Henry F., undated; cuid1453 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Honser, George, undated; cuid1454 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hooper, John W., 1954; cuid1455 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hoover, Charles W., Jr., undated; cuid1456 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hora, Michael, undated; cuid1457 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Horn, Paul, undated; cuid1458 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Horton, Edward Everett, 1967; cuid1459 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Horton, Lishia, undated; cuid1460 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Horvath, John S., 1980; cuid1461 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Horwitch, Mel, undated; cuid1462 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Hostetter, undated; cuid1463 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Hotzler, Russell K., undated; cuid1464 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Houlihan, undated; cuid1465 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Houser, George G., undated; cuid1466 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Houston, Theodore Warren, 1960; cuid1467 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Howard, C. Douglas, undated; cuid1468 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Howley, Eamon, undated; cuid1469 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Huber, Robert E., undated; cuid1470 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hultin, Jerry MacArthur, undated; cuid1471 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Hummel, Susan Flynn, undated; cuid1472 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Hunt, Donald F., undated; cuid1473 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Huseland, Norman, undated; cuid1474 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Hutter, Rudolf, undated; cuid1475 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hyman, Jocette, circa 1996; cuid1476 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Hynn, Robert, undated; cuid1477 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- I
  - Iacono, John, undated; cuid1478 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Iacono, Margie, cuid1479 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Iafrate, G., undated; cuid1480 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Iftekhar, Lamia, 2009; cuid1481 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Immergut, Edmund H., 1979; cuid1482 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Ingham, Joanne, 1999; cuid1483 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Ingram, Maxwell, undated; cuid1484 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Iorio, Jeffrey, undated; cuid1485 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Ip, Tak-Cheung, undated; cuid1486 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Irani, Ray R., undated; cuid1487 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Iskander, Magued, undated; cuid1488 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Ivanoff, Donald, 2002; cuid1489 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- J
  - Jacobs, Eddy, undated; cuid1490 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Jacobs, Joseph J., 1936, 1975, 1978, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1986, 1990, 1994; cuid1491 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Jacobs, Linda, 1993; cuid1492 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Jacobs, Zena, undated; cuid1493 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Jahnke, Craig C., undated; cuid1494 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - James, Dorothy, undated; cuid1495 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Jansen, Albert F.W., undated; cuid1496 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Jansen, Colleen, undated; cuid1497 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Janssen, Gimter, 1939; cuid1498 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Jazwinski, Arthur, undated; cuid1499 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Jear, E., undated; cuid1500 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Jenkins, Carol, undated; cuid1501 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Jiang, Zhong-Ping, undated; cuid1502 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Johnson, Anthony, 1980s; cuid1503 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Johnson, D.H., undated; cuid1504 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Johnson, I. Birger, 1980; cuid1505 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Jones, Barry, undated; cuid1506 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Jones, Francis T., undated; cuid1507 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Jonsson, Eric, undated; cuid1508 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Jordan, Peter, 1995; cuid1509 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Juran, Ilan, undated; cuid1510 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Jung, Check K., undated; cuid1511 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Juretschke, Hellmut J., undated; cuid1512 (Box 4, Folder 129)
- K
  - Kabasakalian, Peter, undated; cuid1513 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Kaczmarek, Richard F., 1973; cuid1514 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Kadik, Abdelhamid, undated; cuid1515 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Kahn, Alexander, undated; cuid1516 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Kahn, Herman (1922-1983), undated; cuid1517 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Kahn, Sophie, undated; cuid1518 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Kahne, Stephen, undated; cuid1519 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Kalil, James, undated; cuid1520 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Kalkhoran, Iraj M., undated; cuid1521 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Kalotay, Andrew, undated; cuid1522 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Kammen, Michael, undated; cuid1523 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Kane, Jasper, 1995; cuid1524 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Kangas, Edward A., 2000; cuid1525 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Kapfer, (William H.), undated; cuid1526 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Kapila, Vikram, undated; cuid1527 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Kaplan, David, undated; cuid1528 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Kaplan, Helene, undated; cuid1529 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1957; cuid1530 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Kaplan, Seymour, 1986; cuid1531 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Kappaz, Michael H., 2010; cuid1532 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Kappenburg, William, undated; cuid1533 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Karnaugh, Maurice, undated; cuid1534 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Karri, Ramesh, undated; cuid1535 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Kasper, Victor Jr., undated; cuid1536 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Kastarelos, Konstantinos, undated; cuid1537 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Katchalski (Katzir), Ephraim, 1973, 1979; cuid1538 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Katsaggelos, Aggelos K., 1986; cuid1539 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Katz, J. Lawrence, undated; cuid1540 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Katz, Larry W., undated; cuid1541 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Katzen, Raphael, 1977; cuid1542 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Kaufman, Harold, 1986; cuid1543 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Kaufman, Michael D., 1996; cuid1544 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Kavanagh, Thomas C., undated; cuid1545 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Keenan, A.J., 1974; cuid1546 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Kellogg, Brainerd, undated; cuid1547 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Kelly, John, undated; cuid1548 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Kemp, L. Franklin, undated; cuid1549 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Kemper, Joseph, undated; cuid1550 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Kerge, Steve, undated; cuid1551 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Kerr, Michelle, undated; cuid1552 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Kershenbaum, Aaron, undated; cuid1553 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Kertesz, Dennis J., undated; cuid1554 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Keyworth, George A., undated; cuid1555 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Khaimchayev, Tamara, undated; cuid1556 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Khan, Eakalak, undated; cuid1557 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Khobot, Liz, undated; cuid3617 (Box 4, Folder 174B)
  - Khorrami, Farshad, 1995; cuid1558 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - King, Carolyn D., undated; cuid1559 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Kinsey, Henry R., undated; cuid1560 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Kirk, Raymond E., 1955; cuid1561 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Kjeldaas, Terje, undated; cuid1562 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Kleiner, Eugene, 1986; cuid1563 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Kline, Tom, undated; cuid1564 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Klosner, Jerome, 1978; cuid1565 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Knudson, John Immanuel, 1935, 1953, 1954; cuid1566 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Kobayakawa, Shinya, 1998; cuid1567 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kobayashi, Koji, undated; cuid1568 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Ed, udnated; cuid1569 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Koehler, George R., undated; cuid1570 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Koeing, undated; cuid1571 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Korfage, Willard, undated; cuid1572 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Korman, Samuel, 1956; cuid1573 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Korniczky, Stephen S., undated; cuid1574 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kossay, David, 1959; cuid1575 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kouar, Mohammed, undated; cuid1576 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kozol, Lauren, undated; cuid1577 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kramer (Kramer-Koehler), Pamela E., 1978, 1986; cuid1578 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kramer, William, 2002; cuid1579 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kreiling, Fred, 1979; cuid1580 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kremer, Richard H., undated; cuid1581 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kriftcher, Noel N., 2002; cuid1582 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kristol, Irving, undated; cuid1583 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kubat, Joseph E., undated; cuid1584 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kuiken, Kathryn, undated; cuid1585 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kumar, Sunil, undated; cuid1586 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kunhardt, Erich, 1986; cuid1587 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kuo, Spencer P., 1995, 1999; cuid1588 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kurz, Ludwik, 1986; cuid1589 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kwartler, A., circa 1968; cuid1590 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kwei, T.K., undated; cuid1591 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- L
  - Lago, James, cuid1592 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Lai, Jai-Lu L. (J.L.), undated; cuid1593 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - LaMarsh, John, 1974; cuid1594 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Lan, Chuan-Tan Edward, undated; cuid1595 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Landis, undated; cuid1596 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lando, Jerome, undated; cuid1597 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Landau, Gad. M., undated; cuid1598 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Lane, "Coach", 1955; cuid1599 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Lane, V. Hugo, undated; cuid1600 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lannon, John, undated; cuid1601 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Larkin, Michael, 1997; cuid1602 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lassen, Walter C., 1979; cuid1603 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Laster, Richard, 1974; cuid1604 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - LaTourette, James, undated; cuid1605 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Lauren, Sidney, undated; cuid1606 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Lawson, Richard, circa 1937; cuid1607 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lederman, Peter, 1964; cuid1608 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lee, Bernard S., undated; cuid1609 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lee, C., undated; cuid1610 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Lee, David M., undated; cuid1611 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Lee, Marvin, undated; cuid1612 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Lee, Tommy, undated; cuid3618 (Box 5, Folder 46B)
  - Leeb, Leonard, 1978; cuid1613 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Lehman, Sheila, undated; cuid1614 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Leiber, Frank, undated; cuid1615 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Leistner, William E, 1985; cuid1616 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - LeKashman, John Q., 1974; cuid1617 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Lemelson, Jerome H., 1995, 1999; cuid1618 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Lender, Samuel, undated; cuid1619 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Lengyel, Emil, 1938; cuid1620 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Lentz, Robert H., undated; cuid1621 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Leonard, Martha R., 1987; cuid1622 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - LePaw, Sylvia, undated; cuid1623 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lenz, Edward, 1937; cuid1624 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Leung, Kok-Ming, 1998; cuid1625 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Levi, Enrico, 1998; cuid1626 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Levine, Nathan, undated; cuid1627 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Levitt, Ian, undated; cuid1628 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Levon, Kalle, 1997, 2000; cuid1629 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Levy, Joel H., undated; cuid1630 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Levy, Leon, 1992, 1998; cuid1631 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Levy, Stephen, undated; cuid1632 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Lewin, Menachem, undated; cuid1633 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Lewis, James P., undated; cuid1634 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Lewis, Robert E., 1960, 1966; cuid1635 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Li, Joan, circa 1996; cuid1636 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lian, Kenneth, undated; cuid1637 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Libby, Paul, undated; cuid1638 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Liccardi, Anthony, undated; cuid1639 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Lieber, Art, undated; cuid1640 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Lieberman, Burton, undated; cuid1641 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Likel, Harry C., undated; cuid1642 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Likourezos, George, undated; cuid1643 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Lin, Feng-Bao, undated; cuid1644 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lin, Li-Chieh, undated; cuid1645 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Lindenauer, Abraham, undated; cuid1646 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Lindholm, undated; cuid1647 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Lindsay, John, undated; cuid1648 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Link, O. Winston, 1995; cuid1649 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Link, O. Winston -- Photos by, undated; cuid1650 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Linton, Jonathan D., undated; cuid1651 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Linza, Stuart, undated; cuid1652 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Lipitz, Elliott A., undated; cuid1653 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Lippman, undated; cuid1654 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Litt, Benjamin, undated; cuid1655 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Littlejohn, Lomax, undated; cuid1656 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Liwschitz-Garik [?], 1942; cuid1657 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Lobenberg, Michel, undated; cuid1658 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Loebl, Ernest M., undated; cuid1659 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lombarden, undated; cuid1660 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Lombardino, Joseph G., undated; cuid1661 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lombardo, George A., undated; cuid1662 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Lord, Thomas, circa 1987; cuid1663 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Lorenz, Patricia A., 1998; cuid1664 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Low, Seth, circa 1866; cuid1665 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Lowe, Bill, undated; cuid1666 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Lowe, Helen, undated; cuid1667 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Lu, I-Tai, undated; cuid1668 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Lubell, Peter, 2001; cuid1669 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Luna, Anthony, undated; cuid1670 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Lundberg, Robert, undated; cuid1671 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Luntey, Eugene H., undated; cuid1672 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Lurie, Harold, 1979; cuid1673 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Lutwak, Erwin, undated; cuid1674 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Lutwick, Larry, undated; cuid1675 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Lybeck, Al, undated; cuid1676 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Lynch, James E., 1960; cuid1677 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Lynch, Patrick "Pat", undated; cuid1678 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Lynch, William A., undated; cuid1679 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Lynford, Jeffrey, undated; cuid1680 (Box 5, Folder 114)
- M
  - MacDiarmid, Alan G., undated; cuid1681 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - MacDonald, Kathleen, undated; cuid1682 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - MacDuff, John N., undated; cuid1683 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Maciag, Robert J., 1986, 1993; cuid1684 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Mack, Edward, circa 1905; cuid1685 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - MacKenzie, Lt. Col. F., 1968; cuid1686 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Maggio, Edward, undated; cuid1687 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Maillacheruvu, Krishnanand Y. "Kris", undated; cuid1688 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Mainiero, Michael, undated; cuid1689 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Malament, undated; cuid1690 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Maloof, Roula, undated; cuid1691 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Mancuso, Michael Jr., undated; cuid1692 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Mandelbaum, Richard, circa 1993; cuid1693 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Mandl, undated; cuid1694 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Manniello, John B. Louis, 1972; cuid1695 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Mansfield, Joseph, circa 1964; cuid1696 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Marchesi, W., undated; cuid1697 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Marchi, undated; cuid1698 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Marcus, Rudolph A., 1999; cuid1699 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Marcuvitz, Nathan, 1986; cuid1700 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Marder, Arnold R., 1974, 1981; cuid1701 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Mardus, Fred and Edna, 1980; cuid1702 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Margolin, Harold, undated; cuid1703 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Mark, Hans, 1982; cuid1704 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Mark, Herman: See Herman Mark Collection, undated; cuid1705
  - Markowitz, David, undated; cuid1706 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Marks, James "Buck", circa 1996; cuid1707 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Marks, Leonard, undated; cuid1708 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Marks, Sylvia K., undated; cuid1709 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Marschhausen, George W., undated; cuid1710 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Marshall, Gillian P., undated; cuid1711 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Marshall, John F., undated; cuid1712 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Martcheva, Maia, undated; cuid1713 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Martin, Harold E., undated; cuid1714 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Martinez, Arthur C., 1996; cuid1715 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Martini, Joseph, undated; cuid1716 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Martinovich, Betty, undated; cuid1717 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Martucci, Charles, undated; cuid1718 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Mason, Roger, undated; cuid1719 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Masaryk, Jan, 1941; cuid1720 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Masselos, William, undated; cuid1721 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Massey, Walter E., 2000; cuid1722 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Mastronardi, circa 1975; cuid1723 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Matalon, Moshe, 1978; cuid1724 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Match, Robert K., undated; cuid1725 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Matsuoka, Shiro, undated; cuid1726 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Matthews, Craig C., undated; cuid1727 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Mattiello, Joseph J., undated; cuid1728 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1985; cuid1729 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - May, William F., 1980; cuid1730 (Box 5, Folder 163)